<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Root>
	<Entry>
		<Translation/>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_NATION_CARTHAGE_MOD_STORY</zType>
		<Translation>    Ich bin Hamilkar Barka, father of Hannibal, the great hero of our nation. I served as a general in the carthage army and the romans called me Barq "thunderbolt" because i strike quickly and unexpected.

    I am responsible for creating the strategy which my son Hannibal implemented in the Second Punic War to bring the Roman Republic close to defeat.

    During the last years i was repeatedly severely wounded. I feel like my end is near and i have to prepare my son Hasdrubal for his upcoming responsibilities as the ruler of our great nation.</Translation>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_NATION_EGYPT_MOD_STORY</zType>
		<Translation>    I am Sneferu. I built at least three pyramids that survive to this day and introduced major innovations in the design and construction of pyramids. I am the first king of the fourth dynasty and going to rule Egypt a minimum of 27 full years. 

     To undertake such massive building projects, i would have had to secure an extensive store of labour and materials, this is where my foreign policy played a large part. My conquests into Libya and Nubia served two purposes: Establish an extensive labour force, and gain access to the raw materials in these countries.

    I was able to capture large numbers of people from other nations, make them my prisoners and then add them into my labour force. My military efforts in Libya led to the capture of 11,000 prisoners and 13,100 head of cattle.
    My Son, Cheops, will follow in his fathers’s footsteps once he has learned enough.</Translation>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_NATION_ROME_MOD_STORY</zType>
		<Translation>    I am Augustus, born as Gaius Octavius and adopted by the great Gaius Julius Caesar. I became the first emperor of the Roman Empire, reigning from 27 BC until my death in AD 14.
		
     Along with Mark Antony, spouse of my sister Octavia, i formed the Second Triumvirate to defeat the assassins of Caesar. My reign initiated an era of relative peace known as the Pax Romana. 

    The future will tell if the greatest nation of all times can outlive the others...</Translation>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_NATION_PERSIA_MOD_STORY</zType>
		<Translation>    I am Xerxes the Great, the fourth King of Kings of the Achaemenid Empire, ruling from 486 to 465 BC. I am the son and successor of Darius the Great and my mother is Atossa, a daughter of Cyrus the Great.
		
     Much of my bad reputation is due to propaganda by the Macedonian king Alexander the Great who had me vilified. One of my greates failures was the failed invasion of Greece in 480 BC.

    However, i successfully crushed the revolts in Egypt and Babylon and afer this i ceased to use the title of 'king of Babylon' calling myself simply 'king of the Persians and the Medes'.</Translation>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_NATION_SPARTA_MOD_STORY</zType>
		<Translation>    I am Leonidas,  "son of the lion" and  warrior king of Sparta. Upon receiving a request from the confederated Greek forces to aid in defending Greece against the Persian invasion. I marched out of Sparta to meet Xerxes' army at Thermopylae with a small force of 1,200 men. My own contribution was just 300 Spartiates.
		
     We faced a Persian army who had invaded from the north of Greece an estimated army of 300,000 men. I sent away the remaining greece troops to secure a retreat option, because i cared for their safety but knowing we Spartiates would never abondon our post on the battlefield.

    The persians took heavy losses but eventually my 300 men and 700 Thespians were surrounded. No one survived and Xerxes orders were to have my head cut off and put on a stake and my body crucified.</Translation>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_NATION_PARTHIA_MOD_STORY</zType>
		<Translation>    I am Orodes, King of Kings of the Parthian Empire. Assisted by my oldest brother Mithridates, we murdered our father.
		
     We quickly fell out and entered into a dynastic struggle, in which i was triumphant. My fight was with the romans - i invaded Armenia and forced king Artavasdes II to submit and abandon his alliance with the Romans.

    Then i invaded Syria, but with little success. Pacorus I, my son and heir was defeated by Cassius. During the Roman Republican civil wars, we sided first with Pompey and then with Brutus and Cassius. I was deeply afflicted by the death of my favourite son, relinquished the throne to my son Phraates.</Translation>
	</Entry>
</Root>
